https://uspages.net/page/privacy-policy

describes the Privacy Policy for
USA Local Business Pages Directory website.
Your Privacy
Your privacy is
important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice
explaining our online information practices and the choices you can
make about the way your information is collected and used. You agree
to agree to these policies by virtue of using our website in a way
that leads to you providing us with personal information.
State Law & Accompanying Rights
Please understand
that you may have additional rights originating from State laws based
on where you live. These State-based rights may augment, strengthen,
or otherwise somehow compliment any privacy rights you have inherently
or under Federal law. Our policy is to comply fully with the privacy
policies of every jurisdiction in which we operate. Accordingly, you
are free to use our Contact information to reach us at any time to
assert any State rights.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For
that reason, our website will never collect or maintain information at
our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of
our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18
are not allowed to use our website and access our services. It is not
our intention to offer products or services to minors.
Google Analytics
USA Local Business Pages Directory uses Google
Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. The tool uses
"cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect
standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information in
an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your
use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to
Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of
this website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the
statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally
Identifiable Information of visitors to our site. Google will not
associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither
we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the
identity of a computer user.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate
settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you
may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By
using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by
Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Other Collection of Personal
Information
When visiting our website, the IP address used to access our website
may be logged along with the dates and times of access. This
information is purely used to analyze trends, administer our website,
track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for
internal use such as statistical assessments and website improvement.
Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to
personally identifiable information.
Other information may be collected as well, which is rather typical of
most websites. For instance, the source that referred you to our
website is generally known. Likewise, your duration on our website,
and your destination when you leave our website can also be tracked.
Other common data collected includes the type of operating system the
computer you are using to access our website has. Similarly, the type
of web browser is often noted. Again, this is common data collection,
and helps ultimately produce a better end-user experience.
Cookies are another common internet practice. Cookies are a key means
of improving user experience by allows us to customize your use of our
website. Simple information is transferred to your computer to allow
the content and experience to reflect your actions, preferences, and
so on. You should simply make the assumption our website uses cookies,
and note that you are free to make adjustments in your web browser to
disable these or otherwise receive notification of cookies so you can
take whatever desired action you so choose. Please understand that
refusing cookies may cripple some of our website features and render
some aspects useless to you.
At times, you will be fully aware of information received, as you are
the direct source providing it. For instance, you may comment on a
business listing, reply to an email (whether broadcast message or auto
responder), provide an email address, complete a survey, requests SMS,
or otherwise. Likewise, purchases necessarily involve collecting
certain information, such as credit card information, Paypal
addresses, your physical address for billing and/or shipping, phone
number, and so on. Refusing to provide some of this information may
lead to us being unable to provide you with the products or services
you've requested.
A prime example of limited access to our website is where content may
be protected by a username and password. Whether a username and
password is generated by our website, or created by you, these will
almost always be connected with some other information related to or
connected with you. This is true since much content that is protected
on the internet is subscription based, often paid for. Thus, the
username and password must necessarily be tied to your other account
data. Usernames and passwords, by their very nature, should be kept
private.
Handling of Personal Information
Note that any personal information you provide to others apart from us
or our vendors is wholly optional. As an example, you might disclose
something in a business listing review or comment. That "private"
information is now "public," and we have no control over that. In like
fashion, you sharing information with any other third party not
functioning as a service provider to us puts that information beyond
our control and becomes subject to the policy that party has in place.
Our primary intention for collecting personal and private information
from you is simply to conduct our business. We can use this internally
to better serve you. Accordingly, we see no reason to share your
personal information to other parties and outside interests unless you
have authorized us to do so.
Of course, there are instances where your information is stored with
third party service providers, such as email service providers, as
they provide services that are industry-leading in quality and
security and are far more beneficial to our end user than attempting
such services "in-house." However, you are never required to deal with
any such third party directly, they are limited in how they use your
information, and they cannot sell or transfer it to others in any way.
However, of course, your information does comprise part of an overall
whole. This aggregate of information, by contrast, may be used to
understand our overall user base. Further, we may share this
information about our website visitors as a whole, not individually,
with third parties for various purposes, in our sole discretion.
While we are staunch privacy advocates, there are times when even we
may be forced to abandon these ideals. Just as major search engines
face ongoing compulsion to provide data against their will, so too may
the same occur with our website. Illegal activity or other serious
acts or allegations could create legal liability for our website. In
those cases, we reserve the right to share your information, or else
may simply be compelled to do so by law.
On the other hand, there may be times when we would need to share your
private information in order to protect our own interests. For
instance, in cases of suspected or alleged copyright infringement or
other intellectual property violations, it may be necessary to share
personal information.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick
DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, may use cookies to
serve ads on this website. The use of DART cookies by Google enables
them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to
this website, including past visits, as well as other websites on the
internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content
network privacy policy at the following url
https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ Tracking of
users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own
privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to
track users activities on this website to measure advertisement
effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own
privacy policies, our website has no access or control over these
cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. However, you can
opt out of some, though likely not all, of these cookies in one easy
location at
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Links to Third Party Websites
We have included links on this website for your use and reference. We
are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You
should be aware that the privacy policies of these websites may differ
from our own.
Comments Policy
As you know, Web 2.0 is all about the conversation. But without a few
simple ground rules, that conversation can turn into a shouting match
that discourages others from entering into the fray.
So here is USA Local Business Pages Directory
comments policy. By posting on my website, you agree to the following:
You may comment without registering. You can log-in via Disqus, OpenID,
Twitter, Facebook; or not at all. It's up to you. You may post
anonymously. I don't recommend this, but you may do so if you wish. I
may change this rule if it is abused.
You may post follow-up questions. If you have a question, chances are
you are not alone. Others are likely thinking similarly. Therefore, I
would rather receive your comments on
USA Local Business Pages Directory than via
email. It is a better use of my time to address everyone at once
rather than answer several similar emails.
You may disagree with me. I welcome debate. However, I ask that if you
disagree with me; or anyone else, for that matter; do so in a way that
is respectful. In my opinion, there is way too much shouting in the
public square to tolerate it here.
USA Local Business Pages Directory reserves the
right to delete your comments. This is my website. I don't have an
obligation to publish your comments. The First Amendment gives you the
right to express your opinions on your blog not mine.
Specifically, I will delete your comments if you post something that
is, in my sole opinion, (a)snarky; (b) off-topic; (c) libelous,
defamatory, abusive, harassing, threatening, profane, pornographic,
offensive, false, misleading, or which otherwise violates or
encourages others to violate my sense of decorum and civility or any
law, including intellectual property laws; or (d) "spam" i.e., an
attempt to advertise, solicit, or otherwise promote goods and
services. You may, however, post a link to your site or your most
recent blog post.
You retain ownership of your comments. I do not own them and I
expressly disclaim any and all liability that may result from them. By
commenting on my site, you agree that you retain all ownership rights
in what you post here and that you will relieve me from any and all
liability that may result from those postings.
You grant USA Local Business Pages Directory a
license to post your comments. This license is worldwide, irrevocable,
non-exclusive, and royalty-free. You grant me the right to store, use,
transmit, display, publish, reproduce, and distribute your comments in
any format, including but not limited to a blog, in a book, a video,
or presentation.
In short, my goal is to host interesting conversations with caring,
honest, and respectful people. I believe this simple comments policy
will facilitate this.
CHANGE NOTICE:
As with any of our administrative and
legal notice pages, the contents of this page can and will change over
time. Accordingly, this page could read differently as of your very
next visit. These changes are necessitated, and carried out by
USPages.net, in order to
protect you and our
USPages.net website. If this page is important to you, you
should check back frequently as no other notice of changed content
will be provided either before or after the change takes effect.
COPYRIGHT WARNING:
The legal notices and
administrative pages on this website, including this one, have been
diligently drafted by an attorney. We at
USPages.net have paid to
license the use of these legal notices and administrative pages on
USPages.net for your
protection and ours. This material may not be used in any way for any
reason and unauthorized use is policed via Copyscape to detect
violators.
QUESTIONS/COMMENTS/CONCERNS:
If you have any questions about
the contents of this page, or simply wish to reach us for any other
reason, you may do so by following this link:
DMCA Compliance - Anti Spam Policy - Contact
USPages.net does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any of the information, content or advertisements contained on, distributed through, or linked, downloaded or accessed from any of the services contained on this website nor the quality of any products, information or other materials displayed, or obtained by you as a result of an advertisement or any other information or offer in or in connection with the service. You hereby acknowledge that any reliance upon any information shall be at your sole risk. USPages.net reserves the right, in its sole discretion and without any obligation, to make improvements to, or correct any error or omissions in any portion of the service. The service and the information herein are provided by USPages.net on an "as is" basis, and USPages.net expressly disclaims any warranties, express or implied, including without linitation warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, concerning the service or any information and products. In no event shall USPages.net be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages of any kind whatsoever concerning the service, the information and the products.
Copyright 1997 2020. USPages.net - All Rights Reserved - USA Local Business Pages Directory.
